<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Main quests on POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>/main-quests/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Main quests on POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 15:39:54 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/main-quests/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Quests And Album Track List</title>
      <link>/main-quests/main-quests-and-album-track-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 15:39:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/main-quests-and-album-track-list/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 341 PM
flase || ture
There&amp;rsquo;s a fat gap in the log right now. Moving to San Mateo has been a little life changing, and when life&amp;rsquo;s good I tend to not write as much. But now it&amp;rsquo;s time to hunker down and focus on a strong tracklist for the poliwat debut.
Tracklist  Intro She Breaking Glass Ceiling Grasshopper my Grasshopper Internet will not be homogenized Trapt in the Womb Lessons from the Drunk Shaman  almost 6a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakland And Sf Are Wild</title>
      <link>/main-quests/oakland-and-sf-are-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 13:25:33 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/oakland-and-sf-are-wild/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 1:25 PM
On caltrain heading from SF to San Mateo. Spent the night in Oakland and This is an audio journal
When I&amp;rsquo;m going through something hard I write, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t the time to write. This is the time for action
Build this, by the end of the day sending it to about 20-30 local venues and nice event buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth Of Ganzoop</title>
      <link>/main-quests/birth-of-ganzoop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 16:32:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/birth-of-ganzoop/</guid>
      <description> At aws worker space in SF
The art of underthinking
late to the chase but on time in my own race  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day One Tss Im Gonna Kil It</title>
      <link>/main-quests/day-one-tss-im-gonna-kil-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2017 10:05:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/day-one-tss-im-gonna-kil-it/</guid>
      <description>Monday 1006 AM
post to IG, FB, Snapchat 1000 Confucious Canoes Sims Sims progress Poliwat progress Clean something Drop a secret note Youtube edu
Clean Bathroom Clear garage Sell something on Let Go
echo boy vst - redbone
Monday 253 PM
Jack lied about the room being ready for me. It was full of stuff, we worked on moving a lot of it out into the garage but the garage is full of stuff so it&amp;rsquo;s going to take a couple days to fully move in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IMoved</title>
      <link>/main-quests/imoved/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 23:34:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/imoved/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 1135PM
Made it to Jack&amp;rsquo;s! 3 calls with the bank Living on credit Chore list Find screens and stick them on windows clean bathroom
Dailies
post to IG, FB, Snapchat 1000 Confucious Canoes Sims Sims progress Poliwat progress Clean something Drop a secret note Youtube edu  In the meeting for TSS tomorrow, we&amp;rsquo;re going to pick a date and request the venue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sometimes</title>
      <link>/main-quests/sometimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 11:02:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/sometimes/</guid>
      <description>saturday 1102 AM
sometimes
I like condiments more than people
1256 pm
daily dose of affirmation

608 PM
Enjoying the last night before a season of sobriety. This journals going to get lit.
Jack laid down the law over the phone earlier- I am to not piss his mom off, help clean out the garage, and do a list of chores. Oh and have a check ready for 200 bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SD SD SD SD SD</title>
      <link>/main-quests/sd-sd-sd-sd-sd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 09:18:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/sd-sd-sd-sd-sd/</guid>
      <description>listening to the new four tet album Who e=mc^2 I call when I&amp;rsquo;m depressed?
I woke up from 3 bad dreams on the trampoline. I&amp;rsquo;m feeling quite lonely. My dad is cursing and is angry about being late to work. The moment he comes home from his job he turns off and veggetizes. We rarely play music together.
Why should I feel depressed? I successfully launched two sites and applied to about 30 jobs yesterday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irony, Trends, Love, and Painkillers</title>
      <link>/main-quests/trends-love-and-painkillers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:05:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/trends-love-and-painkillers/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 1105AM
I have to have to be honest. Other than logging an audio trail, this diary is a tool for me to make better decisions. It was MONDAY when I started my portfolio site, and now I&amp;rsquo;m sitting here and it&amp;rsquo;s late Thursday morning. I woke up on the trampoline falling asleep to Joe Rogon and Neil de Grasse Tyson. At about 1:20:50 Tyson talks about the importance of the naming of stuff, which clearly explains to me why the Illest Village project works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Transcendental Number</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-transcendental-number/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 23:07:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-transcendental-number/</guid>
      <description>The Transcendental Number
Wed 1108 PM
 pi is a trans number  Internet went down
78% nitrogen in the air
It&amp;rsquo;s hard being this vulnerable I want to stop but I can&amp;rsquo;t because being vulnerable makes you strong strong boop boop
got 1000 confucious canoes in
played skip bo with bonnie
Was in a foul mood until hanging out with Mila for an hour. Babies are cool. it was &amp;lsquo;tummy time&amp;rsquo; where Bonnie lies down next to her in the baby room with Mila&amp;rsquo;s head tilted to the right, on her stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Room</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:19:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-room/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 919 AM
Today I can already feel. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a good day. I&amp;rsquo;ll mindlessly and endlessly produce. Today marks the day I need to empty this childhood bedroom of all my shit, which I&amp;rsquo;m going to move up to San Mateo.
Listening to 2000 hits
Dad&amp;rsquo;s extra nice because my mom&amp;rsquo;s stressed out, it&amp;rsquo;s make it or break her heart if I don&amp;rsquo;t do a good job. Good thing I&amp;rsquo;ll rock it because this is EASY MOMM!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Budget Productions But We Got Sammuel Beckett</title>
      <link>/main-quests/no-budget-productions-but-we-got-sammuel-beckett/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 10:21:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/no-budget-productions-but-we-got-sammuel-beckett/</guid>
      <description>Monday 1021 AM
Last night I planted some iceplant Paul gave me in my parents backyard. It&amp;rsquo;s always good to plant on the side.
This morning started with a quick look into Samuel Beckett and three Jays. JK, not marijuana but James Joyce, and Jane Austin.
Quick nugs from School of life and my own understanding:
Sammuel Beckett  likes to write around the word &#39;perhaps&#39; not specific, allowing viewer to make it specific on their own  James Joyce  Everyday losers are just as epic and interesting as rich / heroes / heroines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ostinato Rigore- The Kybalion and Life After 1000 Confucious Canoes 🛶</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-kybalion-and-life-after-1000-confucious-canoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 11:47:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-kybalion-and-life-after-1000-confucious-canoes/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 1148 AM
Just waking up. I ate my dad&amp;rsquo;s unfinished cereal with mangos, bananas, and strawberries in it.
The 7 Hermetic Principles  “THE ALL is MIND; The Universe is Mental.”
 “As above, so below; as below, so above.”
 “Nothing rests; everything moves; everything vibrates.”
 “Everything is Dual; everything has poles; everything has its pair of opposites; like and unlike are the same; opposites are identical in nature, but different in degree; extremes meet; all truths are but half-truths; all paradoxes may be reconciled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 48 Laws Of Power</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-48-laws-of-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 11:23:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-48-laws-of-power/</guid>
      <description>Never outshine the master
 Never put too much trust in friends
👩🏽‍🌾 Learn how to use enemies  Conceal your intentions
👩🏽‍🌾 The Marquis de Sevigne  Always say less than necessary
 So Much depends on Reputation
👩🏽‍🌾 Guard it with your life 👩🏽‍🌾 Erwin Rommel, the soldier everyone was afraid to face.  Court Attention at all costs
👩🏽‍🌾 Pablo would rather paint something disgusting than something ignored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Sisters Birthday</title>
      <link>/main-quests/my-sisters-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 18:16:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/my-sisters-birthday/</guid>
      <description>Fri 617 PM
With my parental units, we are on our way to Bonnie&amp;rsquo;s Birthday dinner at a restaurant named Ember.
My parents watch master chef and eat mcdonalds.
So past 24 hours of poliwat venturing.
 Sean took me to his dad&amp;rsquo;s shop. We opened jars of screws and found enough for at least half the mounting brackets for the sliders / effects racks.   Borrowed a self-powered breadboard from Sean in order to diagnose LEDS, as well as two books on solid state electronics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The School of Life - 1200 Lines Of Code, and Good Design Principles</title>
      <link>/main-quests/1200-lines-of-code-and-good-design-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 11:23:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/1200-lines-of-code-and-good-design-principles/</guid>
      <description>1123 AM
I must admit here that I could be going faster. But I got distracted by the school of life&amp;rsquo;s art and Architecture educational videos on youtube.
Good design:[10]  is innovative – The possibilities for progression are not, by any means, exhausted. Technological development is always offering new opportunities for original designs. But imaginative design always develops in tandem with improving technology, and can never be an end in itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Saiyan Chamber Day 2 And A Chomsky Circuit</title>
      <link>/main-quests/super-saiyan-chamber-day-2-and-a-chompsky-circuit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:29:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/super-saiyan-chamber-day-2-and-a-chompsky-circuit/</guid>
      <description>Wed 1130 AM
 Poliwat master doc is getting an update.
1232 PM
Only listening to Bach because we share a birthday. Ate a quick tri-tip sandwich with a pickle, and made one for my mom.
Since today the world is ending, the only sane task at hand is to do what I love. I will build poliwat, and then travel the world with it. It&amp;rsquo;s that simple. It&amp;rsquo;s not that simple though because although the code compiles, I can&amp;rsquo;t get anything out of the LCD screen at the moment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Hours A Day</title>
      <link>/main-quests/12-hours-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 11:41:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/12-hours-a-day/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1141 AM
creation spawns from chaos
creating aand trading realities as art
life and the imagination is this oric field that surrounds the transcendential object
239 pm
only poliwat
I have cut off all contact with everyone at this point. I will do the bare minimum communications. The only contact is with my parents here. Other than that I am entering complete isolation with myself and poliwat.
This week is devoted to building muscles, and not just physical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit Card for a uHaul but change of plans, my own Masafuera</title>
      <link>/main-quests/moving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 08:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/moving/</guid>
      <description>Monday 8 52 AM
Woke up very depressed
I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to move to San Mateo today. The plan is to start with getting a credit card at Wells Fargo, so I can rent the uhaul. You can&amp;rsquo;t rent a uhaul without a credit card. Then I just have to pack up whats in my room and head up there. But really I&amp;rsquo;d rather turn off my phone, keep my blinds shut, and work on poliwat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Deep Sleep</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-deep-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 20:32:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-deep-sleep/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 833 pm
Dienrich&amp;rsquo;s diary
“Nowadays, the prevailing view is that you should authentically rejoice and celebrate the spiritual happiness that this era has to offer, for it is a gift! People need to think about how many challenges the world has faced and how many obstacles and dreadful dangers it has overcome. They no longer believe that it is temporal distance that embellishes things, persons and situations and what makes difficulties and problems fade away and be forgotten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Sea Diving And Living The Shining</title>
      <link>/main-quests/deep-sea-diving-and-living-the-shining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 19:44:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/deep-sea-diving-and-living-the-shining/</guid>
      <description>I discovered one of the biggest thrills.
But first I will begin with the start of the night, at an old engineer type friend named Thomas from back in my Community College days. He held the BBQ at a house real close to one of the elementary schools I went to. It was interesting because I remember doing motocross as a kid with a friend that used to live there. There used to be a huge nice dirt motocross track in the backyard, but it had since been bulldozed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Is Why Im Broke</title>
      <link>/main-quests/this-is-why-im-broke/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 19:47:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/this-is-why-im-broke/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m broke because I stopped working my web development job over a month ago. I&amp;rsquo;m out of money. I&amp;rsquo;m on a spending freeze. Being home is useful for that.
We were joking the other night and Chad said a good one &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m so broke my most broke friend said I was broke&amp;rdquo;
When you are this broke you can see price tags on all your possessions. I made a pact to sell anything that isn&amp;rsquo;t related to Poliwat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing A Door And The Secret Bus Photo Op</title>
      <link>/main-quests/installing-a-door-and-the-secret-bus-photo-op/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 18:14:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/installing-a-door-and-the-secret-bus-photo-op/</guid>
      <description>Thursday 615 PM
I&amp;rsquo;m on a toliet. Diahrea is running out of my ass while Chopin&amp;rsquo;s Scherzo No. 2 in B flat plays.
There&amp;rsquo;s an interesting mechanic humans do. I know I have Diahrea because once again I opened my day with an empty stomach and 3 cups of coffee. The stomach is no longer empty but I still have a black cup of coffee, right here with me on the toliet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working On Sound Map And Family Hates Me</title>
      <link>/main-quests/working-on-sound-map-and-family-hates-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 10:00:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/working-on-sound-map-and-family-hates-me/</guid>
      <description>Wed 1001 AM
The sound map in Google Earth is going well. I look forward to travelling and adding all audio logs as points, then you can hit play and watch audio trails.
Google Earth is my Sheikah Slate I love this Todd linked it and I need to throw him 20 bucks https://earth.nullschool.net/#current/particulates/surface/level/overlay=pm1/azimuthal_equidistant=22.32,-219.67,225/loc=98.706,20.022
The youtube video editor is useless
Listening to Pirates of Penzance and Fiddler on the Roof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Painting A Wall</title>
      <link>/main-quests/painting-a-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 12:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/painting-a-wall/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1205 PM
Lets be honest I woke up 20 minutes ago. Was up until about 4 making this with Kevin:
Listening to it the morning after and I know how I can make it much better. But the beat philosophy is to hone in
 N64 type beat zelda type beat
221 PM
While dad and I painted to Marquettiquette I thought of the audio map I started on google earth last night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>911 And The Blind Shake</title>
      <link>/main-quests/911-and-the-blind-shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 14:26:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/911-and-the-blind-shake/</guid>
      <description>Monday 226 PM
Today I found out the real founder of 911 was blind, and he spent some time in New York.
Moving and cleaning the room Day 2, very deep in it.
Moving gives you an air of sentiment. There are great as well as painful memories, and they&amp;rsquo;re all treasured. The time capsule box has been selected and I have my items chosen to go inside, a fake degree Sean the provost handed me at graduation, and unopened Yoshi toy from Mcdonalds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Inventory and Captured Memories</title>
      <link>/main-quests/beat-inventory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 15:24:24 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/beat-inventory/</guid>
      <description>502 pm
Captured memories is a main quest in Zelda. You need to find these 12(or 13?) lost memories across the expansive regions of the game.
Operation Captured Memories is the new official code name for the time capsule that we are burying at a graveyard in a couple weeks. So far this is what the box has:
 graduation certificiate from UCSC (which I&amp;rsquo;ll write a letter to my future self on) yoshi model from Mcdonalds little note I left for Tara (Jordan Lipaz&amp;rsquo;s GF) when I visited her trailer at the trailer park  &amp;lt;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mila Likes Reggae</title>
      <link>/main-quests/mila-likes-reggae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 17:14:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/mila-likes-reggae/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 515 PM
Mom is babysitting Mila for the first time. She likes Raggae
It&amp;rsquo;s time to go back online. I&amp;rsquo;ve been sick since Monday, and still have a nasty cough. I feel weak and fat.
Going to retroactively share what happened on the off days, and finally work on poliwat.
My Zelda botw binge has been relentless. I love storming Ganon&amp;rsquo;s castle and hunting down lynels. I want to make a music video with actual gameplay on something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Farming</title>
      <link>/main-quests/dragon-farming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 17:25:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/dragon-farming/</guid>
      <description>fridat 525 pm
zelda in my room day 5 of being sick
where did the time go?
Why is it so difficult to get my Nintendo Switch screenshots to my lappy?
you forget yourself</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashleys Photography</title>
      <link>/main-quests/ashelys-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 17:53:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/ashelys-photography/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m getting stuck on Ashley&amp;rsquo;s Photography work. I can&amp;rsquo;t look away! If she had a genre of photos I would call it sexy magic. She exploits the setting around these people to look much more attractive and magical than they&amp;rsquo;re probably treated. The hopeless romantic in me says the magic and beauty are already there, while she uses photography to show and remind others of it.
Future tracks will have track art from Ashley and will be notated as such.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sicker Than Poopoo</title>
      <link>/main-quests/sicker-than-poopoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 15:55:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/sicker-than-poopoo/</guid>
      <description>wed 3555 pm
I&amp;rsquo;m so sick the sickest sicker than a dog sicker than poopoo!
I can barely sit up straight
been a good slave today making beats in chads room his parents are gone
and a thought occurred to me what if my future love is able to read this?
this is the first time I considered this. Should I write you a message? If I do it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be that easy to find&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ILLEST VILLAGE,  DayQuil Type Beat</title>
      <link>/main-quests/dayquil-type-beat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 17:34:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/dayquil-type-beat/</guid>
      <description>Very sick.
one more time for good measure
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth Of Illest Village aka got chased by a drunk guy</title>
      <link>/main-quests/birth-of-illest-village/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 17:30:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/birth-of-illest-village/</guid>
      <description>Illest Village is the group name for the beats I make with Chad and Kevin, (also Chris and Sean when I see them).
We have so many beats we&amp;rsquo;ve made together, and this latest batch has shown some good progress. I only like one of these but the others were very fun to make with them :D
 rick and morty type beat family guy type beat racy grandma type beat raiders type beat divorce type beat affair type beat</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pauls Bday From Heatwave To Thunderstorm</title>
      <link>/main-quests/pauls-bday-from-heatwave-to-thunderstorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 17:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/pauls-bday-from-heatwave-to-thunderstorm/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 526 PM
Haven&amp;rsquo;t written much because life has been too good.
In the car with Kevin and chad, we&amp;rsquo;re hitting paul&amp;rsquo;s b day!!!!
Very excited.
I took a bath in a horse troph in my parents backyard. I got everyone I love all about jimmothy leary.
Last night a drunk guy stumbled upon us and it&amp;rsquo;s still hilarious.
Me leaving my new hard drive in santa cruz was a huge mistake, but it&amp;rsquo;ll work out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hashtagAverage</title>
      <link>/main-quests/another-average-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 11:46:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/another-average-day/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 1146 AM
Joey made this using my piano he chopped up! Him and Enoch worked on this together and I love it.
 Saturday 342 PM
&amp;ldquo;knowledge, in the cloud, in a tree, in the cloud&amp;rdquo; - Mr. Smith Been making wires, figuring out the breadboard setup, and working with just the teensy 3.6 for poliwat. Sampled peter playing the desk and now I want to make a quick little midi controller with the teensy so that we can play the desk kit :) Going to coffee and do confucious canoes for a 10 minute break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature Rewards Courage</title>
      <link>/main-quests/nature-rewards-courage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:15:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/nature-rewards-courage/</guid>
      <description>1218 PM, Friday
Cleaning out my desk, turning in my gun and badge. Last day at work, no one is here. Peter will arrive shortly and we will move stuff. I&amp;rsquo;m hangingout around because this guy Brent had my hard drive and he&amp;rsquo;s usually around here at this time. He may be going on a trip however, so I may have to leave town without it!
https://youtu.be/OzmeBkrBcOU
1205 am</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joeys Site</title>
      <link>/main-quests/joeys-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:27:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/joeys-site/</guid>
      <description>amidst moving, jamming, joking joeys site will have his services
mixing and mastering Live Drum Recording Sound Design Composition Foley Beats
making him a site and he will give me some drums lessons
Now You Know by Prickly Pair ^^ his music === I love it !!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Mkultra Declassified</title>
      <link>/main-quests/project-mkultra-declassified/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:06:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/project-mkultra-declassified/</guid>
      <description>spent the day remixing DFW&amp;rsquo;s this is water, here it goes:
#$%^&amp;amp;*)&amp;amp;*&amp;amp;)(&amp;amp;((&amp;amp;(&amp;amp;(&amp;amp;(&amp;amp;(&amp;amp;((*&amp;amp;)))))))))
 other animals bond, but they don&amp;rsquo;t go bananas
don&amp;rsquo;t listen to people when it comes to money
point of the life - a good party
what DNA is trying to do - create what you imagine instantaneously
we addict to each other
secret history of the human race
new part of the human mind
what I learned</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet your favorite author 🔥😌💌</title>
      <link>/main-quests/meet-your-favorite-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 10:57:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/meet-your-favorite-author/</guid>
      <description>WED 1057 AM
Meet your favorite author 🔥😌💌 FRANZEN GOT BACK TO US. Jack and I are very happy. You should go meet your favorite people, right now. Do it. Contact them. Be yourself. Be ridiculous, funny, and loving. I won&amp;rsquo;t log what Franzen said to us just in case he&amp;rsquo;s reading poliwat. I doubt it though, he didn&amp;rsquo;t seem to figure out the .at part 😝 at the end of the url.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When The Found Apple Tree Was Two Meals</title>
      <link>/main-quests/when-the-found-apple-treet-was-two-meals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:19:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/when-the-found-apple-treet-was-two-meals/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1120 AM I&amp;rsquo;m listening to this new solo piano piece I started this morning. I was in a hurry because I woke to a text from the Dentist, I was 30 minutes late. So I ordered a quick lyft, couldn&amp;rsquo;t find my passport which serves a dual function as my wallet, and made it up to campus. Angel told me however that I was too late but she could get me in for a deep cleaning at noon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Never Meet Your Favorite Author and a cop pulled a glock on me</title>
      <link>/main-quests/never-meet-your-favorite-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 03:45:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/never-meet-your-favorite-author/</guid>
      <description>Monday 345 AM It&amp;rsquo;s too early to think clearly. But I find myself wide awake at an hour where coffee is not easy to grab and without filters in my house. I lie in a pile of blankets on a sleeping bag in a white room furnished with only a music stand and a blue lightbulb hanging on the wall.
Yesterday was one of the best days of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freebird By Franzen</title>
      <link>/main-quests/freebird-by-franzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 08:31:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/freebird-by-franzen/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 832 AM
Woke up early so I could get some work done. Katie&amp;rsquo;s coming by with a thermos full of coffee at 10. We will checkout the local graveyard I assume, but it&amp;rsquo;s up in the air.
Tripping out to Slyvia&amp;rsquo;s voice currently. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing. One of the last tracks on our first album as Jimmothy Leary. There&amp;rsquo;s about 10 tracks in my iTunes. James and I spent a lot of time yesterday bouncing tracks and figuring out the order of the album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encyclodpedia Of Silk Magic, Volume 3</title>
      <link>/main-quests/encyclodpedia-of-silk-magic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 22:24:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/encyclodpedia-of-silk-magic/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 1025 PM
Jack and I are reading sections of freedom&amp;gt; We just found the part we&amp;rsquo;re going to rewrite turning the characters into birds.
But let&amp;rsquo;s log yesterday first Friday at work. Never got an email back for + a main work task so I spent the day making this
I drank too much yesterday
-=- Did anyone buy my music? ONE PERSON DID HOLYSHIT -=-
Sunday 1202 AM</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Month In</title>
      <link>/main-quests/one-month-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 00:13:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/one-month-in/</guid>
      <description>it feels good  -16 days sober A quick analysis of an online journal. Currently there are less than 10 readers (the latest being a 71 year old woman) I&amp;rsquo;m finding that there are experiences that need to be documented, but are disadvantageous to write. It isn&amp;rsquo;t a good journal without the experiences that matter to me, so it&amp;rsquo;s a huge disservice to leave those experiences out. I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with simply hiding that content so I can find it at a later date easily but users won&amp;rsquo;t see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masafuera @costco &#43; Prue &#43; to the Birth of jimmothy_leary</title>
      <link>/main-quests/be-harder-on-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 08:50:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/be-harder-on-yourself/</guid>
      <description>masafuera = farther away Thursday 1150 AM
I&amp;rsquo;ve been at work since 930 AM
Spoke with Peter on the phone about dreams.
I went to bounce hour at work, this 1 hour weekly pow-wow where you share what you&amp;rsquo;re working on or do a presentation. I told everyone about PoLIWAT and scheduled to present it on the 28th of September. That&amp;rsquo;s my deadline! To get a working mvp out. I&amp;rsquo;m moving out of SC in about a week, and originally called Peter to see if he&amp;rsquo;d be interested in helping me move out of my place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woke Up In Trong Quans Studio</title>
      <link>/main-quests/woke-up-in-trong-quans-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:37:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/woke-up-in-trong-quans-studio/</guid>
      <description>driving back Cut this in the car to get my editing fix. Used Jack&amp;rsquo;s lappy and some audio he had in itunes, then some guitar I played in the post office last week:
 -=-=&amp;ndash;=- wed 928 AM
IN San Jose we slept in trong quan’s studio
me and steflono Write a release schedule
operation Gameify - Zelda
finish and post patreon account main quests shrine quests side quests</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heaven On Earth</title>
      <link>/main-quests/heaven-on-earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:37:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/heaven-on-earth/</guid>
      <description> isn&amp;rsquo;t a journal entry but I sampled tyler&amp;rsquo;s yoga studio which we slept in  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;River Don&#39;t Run Deep&#39; The Adventures Of Sirpenisis, Miculu Batulu, Steflono, Drunk Shaman, and Gai NayNay</title>
      <link>/main-quests/adventures-of-sirpenisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:14:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/adventures-of-sirpenisis/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1:37 pm
Going to cut a quick eclipse to river experience
the best day of my life
components of the best day in my life (1 of them):
 treehouse jam with friends solar eclipse hanging out on an island on along a river with friends floating down the river straight into downtown, 3 people 1 inner tube  =-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-
The best days of my life are short entries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Adventures Of Mila and Uncle Mike</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-adventures-of-mila-and-uncle-mike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 00:47:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-adventures-of-mila-and-uncle-mike/</guid>
      <description>####### Volume 1
Monday 12 47 AM
What can I say. Woke up on a beach by mad river. The sun shone through the fog, and I recorded this:
 Stefan Jack and I skinny dipped in the ocean. There was a fisherman right next to us who got disgusted and left. We had a hilarious and exciting breakfast in Arcata. I haven&amp;rsquo;t recorded much on account of dead batteries after the ocean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons From A Morning Uber</title>
      <link>/main-quests/lessons-from-a-morning-uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:05:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/lessons-from-a-morning-uber/</guid>
      <description>11 06 AM I find myself on the 17 bus again. My fingers have fresh callous from playing bass for hours yesterday. I&amp;rsquo;m a fan.
The Uber driver had some colorful ideas to share. I oblidged, why not?
The trip isn&amp;rsquo;t off to a great start :)
But I pumped out this with the uber audio I just got:
 Going to focus on organizing my sound library now. Oh and story of my life the lappy has a full tummy it needs to shit out bad tape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If You Do Not Leave Home, Calamity</title>
      <link>/main-quests/if-you-do-not-leave-home-calamity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 13:50:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/if-you-do-not-leave-home-calamity/</guid>
      <description>730 AM
Called dad P Diddy he didn&amp;rsquo;t answer. But he texted me saying I probably stayed up all night. Not this time!
I walked to the abbey, this is my efficacy when the internet goes down:
why won&#39;t the internet work here at the abbey? nothing is working. What a waste of time computers and phones are so fucking stupid I only curse because I haven&#39;t had nicotine in a very long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Hooky Set Sail</title>
      <link>/main-quests/play-hooky-set-sail/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 10:39:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/play-hooky-set-sail/</guid>
      <description>I took the day off and went sailing with my friend
My mindset has completely changed. I&amp;rsquo;m young. I&amp;rsquo;m going to do the stupid unsafe thing for a while. I&amp;rsquo;ll survive. And if I don&amp;rsquo;t there will be a catalog of working documenting my journey. It&amp;rsquo;s all about making tracks based off audio collected from the day.
Chris and I sampled his boat, we call it the old gwen drum kit ahahahaha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Abs Anonymous</title>
      <link>/main-quests/abs-anonymous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:11:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/abs-anonymous/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a new project.
The 12 steps to better abs.
Abs Anonymous.
And it started because for years, I have been keeping tabs on others with the same name as me, Michael Betts. Mostly to feel better about myself, but also I have this fantasy where we can all start a think tank and solve the world&amp;rsquo;s issues. Or even better not solve them and make a show of our attempts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Is A Sacred Circle</title>
      <link>/main-quests/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 11:36:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/life-is-a-sacred-circle/</guid>
      <description>Tuesday 1136 AM
I&amp;rsquo;m supposed to be at work by 10 AM. My boss texted me an hour ago then called, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been glued to this track [stefan]() and I worked on early into the morning. The soundscapes are from our professor and mentor David Dunn, and the woman speaking is my relative Cathy Nelson. Her work is so inspiring an entire album could be made from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back To Office Life</title>
      <link>/main-quests/back-to-office-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 12:46:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/back-to-office-life/</guid>
      <description>Monday 12 46 PM
I&amp;rsquo;ve been at work since 10 AM and have virtually gotten nothing done. (For my job at least). I can&amp;rsquo;t concentrate to save my life. Today I&amp;rsquo;m going to post some stuff up online to sell.
I can&amp;rsquo;t work because life is short. I have songs to work on. I can&amp;rsquo;t stop.
I&amp;rsquo;m a slave. I&amp;rsquo;m a slave to the beat. The family reunion trip changed my mindset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Doneish Late To Train</title>
      <link>/main-quests/album-doneish-late-to-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 16:01:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/album-doneish-late-to-train/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 402 pm
What I&amp;rsquo;m listening to: {}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{}{} -=-
Marquetteiquette - Betts Family Reunion Album Side A by Michael Betts
=-=
####I was just about damn late to the train
Well I was 11 minutes late, but lucky for me I ride Amtrak and they are always late. I even had a few minutes to spare. I forgot my belt, my dad gave me his. I love him so much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from a Drunk Shaman</title>
      <link>/main-quests/my-drunk-shaman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2017 11:33:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/my-drunk-shaman/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 1134 AM A golden rule of writing is to choose specific over vague. The drunk shaman would not appreciate my sharing about them online so I will be vague. You are unstoppable when you have a drunken shaman.
Instead of talking about it I&amp;rsquo;m working on a track. This is the master doc for lyrics and iterations on the music.
  [intro] ( chug a pint ) (different computer voice each word) drunk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Straight From The Hospital Bed</title>
      <link>/main-quests/straight-from-the-hospital-bed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 17:22:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/straight-from-the-hospital-bed/</guid>
      <description>Another unfinished project, but the idea is
song involving the final stage of life, and the lryics are basically your final will and testament. I imagine myself would be angry on my deathbed, and anger is an abstraction from fear. I have too many ideas to execute in one life, and that&amp;rsquo;s why I&amp;rsquo;m angry.
I&amp;rsquo;m freestyling on this version. I was actually lying down on my back, in the dark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back In Cali</title>
      <link>/main-quests/back-in-cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 17:14:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/back-in-cali/</guid>
      <description>Friday 620 pm
Peter hasn&amp;rsquo;t called back again - I called him yesterday.
Chad said he was going to be home in 30 and we were going to walk the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s dogs together. He never showed up and I&amp;rsquo;ve called 3 times. I&amp;rsquo;m very depressed. It&amp;rsquo;s day 2 of sobriety, and my only drug has been in how the day was spent. I worked on the Betts family renunion album from 8am - 6pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 7</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 12:29:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-7/</guid>
      <description>I wish I could share my favorite tape. I wish I could even state what&amp;rsquo;s on the tape as well. But what&amp;rsquo;s life without secrets? I&amp;rsquo;ll take the USGOV approach. In 20 years it won&amp;rsquo;t matter so it will be the declassified tapes.
In the meantime I will share a gem I don&amp;rsquo;t want to forget - Tommy Betts the man who mentored my dad in music, and my father. I&amp;rsquo;m playing some piano in the background, and the recorder I left on their table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 6 OPEN MIKE </title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 12:29:20 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Brian me and Miles went to a Poetry night in Marquette. 3 cousins! That&amp;rsquo;s a novel experience for me so it was quite exciting. Brian and I each spat a poem, and this is the only place that will have audio from that night. Brian is a good writer and him and him and I both share the schizo gene.
++
909
Let me see if I can find it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 5 Best Flute Lecture of my life </title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 12:29:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-5/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 4</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 12:29:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-4/</guid>
      <description>  These two haven&amp;rsquo;t seen each other since Mammoth in 1985. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 3</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 12:29:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-3/</guid>
      <description>My dad and I went to checkout a guitar on craigslist today. It&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;instrumental&amp;rsquo; that we get a guitar on this trip, because the magic and emotions have been running high so far.
We had a great time with him, spent 20 minutes cracking jokes and BSing. Erik is hilarious. Towards the end of the transaction, Erik handed me the jacket seen in the picture above. It is my new favorite jacket, and I&amp;rsquo;m dedicating my next track to Erik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Vortex</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-vortex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 04:14:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-vortex/</guid>
      <description>Saturday 414 AM
I learned a sure of a hell of a lot about the Betts family
Tommy Betts mentored my dad in guitar. Another relative said he came over to Tommy&amp;rsquo;s house one day and said to him at the door &amp;ldquo;Do you drink?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Do you fuck?&amp;rdquo;.
glazed doughnut
Saturday 822 AM
Heading to The Betts Family reunion!
This place has been so inspirational, I put off all other projects to instead create a little Michigan EP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 2</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 12:17:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Got audio of the Lake Superior. A new goal I have is to release my first album on spotify, and it&amp;rsquo;s will simply be an album of different bodies of water I&amp;rsquo;ve recorded 🔥💧😂.
This morning was monumental. I met the most family members in my entire life. We hit the bar Flannigan&amp;rsquo;s ( right next door to the house my dad gew up in ) then the graveyard. That&amp;rsquo;s my grandparents graves on my dad&amp;rsquo;s side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan Day 1</title>
      <link>/main-quests/michigan-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 12:11:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/michigan-day-1/</guid>
      <description> thu 134 am
fuck fuck
fuck i forgot to tell james my check didn&amp;rsquo;t clear
i will now when i shit
fuck rent (both the musical and real life)
My dad hasn&amp;rsquo;t been here in his hometown for 37 years. That&amp;rsquo;s him on the left as a kid.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poliwat Master Doc</title>
      <link>/main-quests/poliwat-master-doc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 11:49:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/poliwat-master-doc/</guid>
      <description>main doc for all things related to the poliwat project. If you can&amp;rsquo;t tell it&amp;rsquo;s the favorite of my projects. The basis of this doc is for my own sanity check. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a tutorial geared for others on the basis of learning, it is geared towards my own private understanding of the status of poliwat.
Wed 101 pm Sept 20th, 2017
A master doc for poliwat has had a long time coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Will Not Be Homogenized</title>
      <link>/main-quests/internet-will-not-be-homogenized/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 11:45:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/internet-will-not-be-homogenized/</guid>
      <description>Contents 1. Instrumental 2. Lyrics / vocal cues 1. Instrumental Chord Pallette 89 BPM
F# G
(matt /jack playing congas in jack’s studio, michael with microhpone) formatted like” https://youtu.be/QnJFhuOWgXg
Song format: [Intro] [Verse] [Verse] [Chorus] [Verse] [Verse] [Chorus] [Bridge] [Chorus] [Chorus]
[pre - chorus] dearfcc.org the internet will not be homogenized the internet will not be homogenized the internet will not be homogenized steam and youtube will always be the same price</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heading To Michigan</title>
      <link>/main-quests/heading-to-michigan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 11:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/heading-to-michigan/</guid>
      <description>Smoked a joint last night. It was the first time in 11 days Tuesday 11 43 AM
On a plane to Chicago with my dad. Then we&amp;rsquo;re catching a flight to Marquette, Michigan.
This flight is all about organizing my sound library, and sharing some secret sound.
###This is more for Bonnie | family data sheet | dad&amp;rsquo;s side - Michigan
Dad&amp;rsquo;s dad was born in &amp;lsquo;Municin&amp;rsquo;
Tuesday 638 PM On the final flight, heading from Chicago to Marquette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Breath When</title>
      <link>/main-quests/how-to-breath-when/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 13:58:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/how-to-breath-when/</guid>
      <description>Homebrew Piano by Michael Betts Just jumped in the ocean and practiced handstands. This guy showed me how to go from your butt to a handstand There are different types of breathing.
 Square breathing
  In middle school my therapist (whose email was hypnohupp) taught me square breathing.
You inhale for 10 seconds, hold for 10, exhale for 10, hold for 10, rinse and repeat.
I like to start at 5 seconds and then increase the time after a few cycles through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chessy The Bus</title>
      <link>/main-quests/chessy-the-bus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 11:19:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/chessy-the-bus/</guid>
      <description>Bus Sessions by Many Humans How many times have you texted someone I love you in a grocery line how many times will I drink a sip too many and say something just outside of bounds but there is no longer a ref to call it how many fouls can you get away with in life, and how? that’s a quora question.
how many times will I fall in love? how many times will I fail before I succeed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aa On A Train</title>
      <link>/main-quests/aa-on-a-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 11:17:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/aa-on-a-train/</guid>
      <description>  no comment </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death Of Panda</title>
      <link>/main-quests/death-of-panda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 11:02:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/death-of-panda/</guid>
      <description>take death in pride
My cat died a few a couple months ago. It occurred around the time that %^&amp;amp;#$% broke up with me. I haven&amp;rsquo;t talked about it since, but being home the past few days I was reminded how much I missed her. { The cat, not my X }
Some tape of my crying mom plus drunk best childhood friend talking of the recent death of our lovely cat, panda</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Screwdrivers</title>
      <link>/main-quests/star-screwdrivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 13:07:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/star-screwdrivers/</guid>
      <description>Sunday 108 PM
I&amp;rsquo;m pissed
real pissed. all I&amp;rsquo;ve got done today is 25 pushups / 50 confucious canooes / took my laptop apart. heading to the store for the second time with my dad to get a bunch of tiny star screwdrivers. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to get a kit of 1-10mm for this time and in the future.
Of the two meetings I scheduled with friends today, both forgot, and I should&amp;rsquo;ve completely been expecting that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lost And Found</title>
      <link>/main-quests/lost-and-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 14:28:03 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/lost-and-found/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s this girl on the train. She has a nice SLR camera. For the past hour She&amp;rsquo;s been sneaking photos of people in the lounge car. She might&amp;rsquo;ve even gotten me, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure.
I got her though  this was recorded on the sixth floor of a stairwell at my uni dorms. I was messing with a made-up, by ear tuning. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what key this is. I&amp;rsquo;m tone deaf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Final TODO List</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-final-todo-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 13:08:54 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-final-todo-list/</guid>
      <description> TBA TBA TBA TBA TBA TBA TBA TBA TBA when I&#39;m ready  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Lecture Of My Undergrad Career</title>
      <link>/main-quests/best-lecture-of-my-undergrad-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 13:02:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/best-lecture-of-my-undergrad-career/</guid>
      <description> TBA </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She Breaking Glass Ceiling</title>
      <link>/main-quests/she-breaking-glass-ceiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 11:38:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/she-breaking-glass-ceiling/</guid>
      <description>saturday 1139 am
boarding a train @noon this project is special I started she breaking glass ceiling last Fall. I made the hook of the track while walking from my dorm to the studio listening to a BADBADNOTGOOD track on repeat. I got the flow of it and wanted to fix the words, it took hours to get it to its final form here;
 You&#39;ll need a lighter to hire her she aspire to conquer perspire till you retire she think in code on computer she walking you stalker she feeling you heeling at uni barely breaking even but breaking glass Ceiling she breaking glass ceiling   Tuesday 253 pm *  I need to find someone to colab with in order to finish this track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grasshopper My Grasshopper</title>
      <link>/main-quests/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 09:47:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/grasshopper-my-grasshopper/</guid>
      <description>incomplete Song set in a meadow where I&amp;rsquo;m walking, and asking a grasshopper I find for some life advice. I proceed to please my case. Grasshopper listens then gives me some generic advice response.
Game is to stick to this master / apprentice relationship with stuff. Keep it cool kung foo, karate kid, kill bill, etc&amp;hellip;
Current state (instrumental)  [intro] - other vocals (MOON) Grasshopper my Grasshoper (6) I need a mentor I need a guru (10) [verse 1] (Michael) Grasshopper my grasshopper (6) I speak to you in total confidence from consequence (14) in pool go go girl went postal in my post office (13) be super nice cause most are lost (8) most are lonely (4) few are loud (3) I am proud (3) Im a prophet of my past predicated upon all my mistakes (12) if I love jimminy cricket spitting to crickets my miss takes (16) I spit to you my Grasshopper (8) [pre-chorus 1] I need a mentor (5) I need a guru (5) I&#39;m not walking on my own (5) || I need a mentor || I cannot take this (5) [chorus] I cannot fake this no more (7) I cannot take this no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) I cannot work here no more (7) [[need more shit]] &amp;lt;b&amp;gt;PreChorus 2&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt; The grasshopper said wax on | wax off?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trapt In The Womb</title>
      <link>/main-quests/trapt-in-the-womb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 09:03:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/trapt-in-the-womb/</guid>
      <description>had 2 beers last night Currently working on a trap song with lyrics exploring the perspective of not being born yet, and not necessarily wanting to be born. Since you&amp;rsquo;re constrained to the reality of our politics, biology, and paradigms; such as religion, capitalism, etc.
current state  I got the idea at my sister&amp;rsquo;s house, when I took an image of her sonogram and ran it through a max msp patch that converted the image data to MIDI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Look Out The Window</title>
      <link>/main-quests/look-out-the-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 08:54:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/look-out-the-window/</guid>
      <description>^^ Call BACK the last day sof the dorms I freestyled over this blog post - that&amp;rsquo;s the audio ^^ Look out the Window
Fantasy task list: Go to this document when needing a title for a track
On caltrain and I have to shit so bad. I have 40 minutes until I hit San Hoe.
Gossip:
Lisa currently won&amp;rsquo;t talk to her dad because he bought a tesla She is also having some sort of relations with a prisoner where she volunteers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Im Sitting On</title>
      <link>/main-quests/what-im-sitting-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 01:11:27 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/what-im-sitting-on/</guid>
      <description>300 gigs of my own personal audio recordings.  ^ fav atm
Saturday 116 AM
The biggest treasure of my life is my recordings. I collect audio every day. Normal slice of life things. I constantly record people without them knowing. I call it guerilla audio, and I&amp;rsquo;m not going to stop. You can tell me it&amp;rsquo;s immoral, illegal, douchie, lock me up, kick my ass, and I still won&amp;rsquo;t stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Center Of Github</title>
      <link>/main-quests/the-center-of-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 23:17:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/the-center-of-github/</guid>
      <description>the center of github
 I have a romantic thought. What’s at the center of Github? I imagine a room where someone makes beats as a 9-5. These beats help fuel the rest of the programming community. This person makes an instrumental track for each git command. Each track has it’s stems available on github.
My day job right now is web development. I am a primarily self taught programmer. I haven’t gone beyond doodling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I, your therapist at wits end</title>
      <link>/main-quests/i-yourtherapist-at-wits-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 23:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/i-yourtherapist-at-wits-end/</guid>
      <description>^^ old class assignment
Friday 533 PM | OnCalTrain | JULY 28 2017 | #####I your therapist at wits end
Had 1 beer @ [jack&amp;rsquo;s]() house and we livestreamed the Sims 3 on Twitch as prep for our play. Just wanted to report on an occurrence that happened a couple months ago. After my last breakup, I went a little off the rails. No, not talking ruby, I maintained a healthy ecosystem of smoke and drink each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Model_parents</title>
      <link>/main-quests/model_parents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 16:38:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/model_parents/</guid>
      <description>I always wished I grew up in a household like this. I wanted nothing more than a laptop since the age of 6, but didn&amp;rsquo;t get my hands on a computer until some extreme manipulation in seventh grade. I got a shitty Dell that would run World of Warcraft at 12 FPS in Ogrimmar or Dalaran. I was an incredibly annoying lock for a while but my real soul was ganking, dueling and general pvping as an undead rogue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pbjmaster_1</title>
      <link>/main-quests/pbjmaster_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 10:30:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/pbjmaster_1/</guid>
      <description>Friday 10:31 AM
Don&amp;rsquo;t start reading until you play this
A major client we have here has a major page down for their international (french site). I really had to shit and drink coffee so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t much help and now I should be working on fixing that, but am also consulting my buddy tyler on some flexbox use for a client of his.
Going to Michigan on Tuesday, so real quick notes, these things have to happen today -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help</title>
      <link>/main-quests/help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 12:19:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/help/</guid>
      <description>Bounce hour
Every week at my work there&amp;rsquo;s an hour where you can share your projects / ideas over free coffee and snacks. I go for the free coffee and snacks.
I don&amp;rsquo;t have any new ideas but listening to all my unfinished beats.
// need to make more music
 Yesterday I failed at making live loops because I didn&amp;rsquo;t have good old DJ Chad Mike hitting record for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>somedays just to live is courage</title>
      <link>/main-quests/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 20:42:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/2/</guid>
      <description>Wed 842 pm July 26 2017-06
I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything to type anymore. I&amp;rsquo;ve been sober for a full 7 days now, and I&amp;rsquo;m pissed. I am angry. I will use this anger to get shit done, like log work hours, work on music
Todd hooked me up big time at the fab lab, and I met Chris and Jordan. Chris Maddox printed the first versions of POLIWAT for me and I&amp;rsquo;m super amped on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The year I was 25</title>
      <link>/main-quests/help1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/main-quests/help1/</guid>
      <description>I dream in POLIWAT  Also my other account sound
I have been completely sober for 5 days Tuesday 952 PM
At Diridon in San Jose. Hopefully the 17 bus comes and I&amp;rsquo;ll get to my place in Santa Cruz before midnight. My laptop charging porter burned out while on the train so this is the last charge until I repair it. I found a shop in San Jose that has a new pot I can install myself for 40 bucks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>